大家听好了
Listen up, alamo people,
所有人全部进候诊室等着
everybody into the waiting room.
如果没有生病 就赶快回家吧
If you are not sick, then please go home.
夜班人员还没开始工作呢
The night shift hasn't even started yet,
而你们已经令人头疼的了
and you're giving everybody a headache.
夜班人员 一分钟之内集合
Night shift, report to duty in one minute.
这要持续多久
How long does this go on?
一整夜
All night.
他们总是源源不断地进来
They just keep trickling in.
每年这些阿拉莫之战的重演者
Every year these alamo reenactors
喝了太多的自制啤酒
drink too much homemade beer.
还吃了太多的红酒煨兔肉
And eat too much rabbit stew.
噢
Ohh!
要清理第三过道了
Mop-up on aisle 3.
不 不 不 不 不
No, no, no, no, no.
听着 如果你来不了 那就不用勉强了
Look, if you can't get here, you can't get here.
视频字幕由 SSK字幕组 制作发布
字幕只供学习 请勿做任何商业行为
敬请关注新浪微博@SSK字幕组
真的 没有关系 只是
No, it's fine. It's just...
我本来希望你能来 因为明天是我的生日 但是
I was hoping that since it's my birthday tomorrow, but --
没事 我真的 明白的
no, I understand, really.
翻译：酥酥 Bezero 濯涟 慕斯 elsa 粒粒肉丝 自画
是的
Yeah.
我们下周再庆祝吧 斯科特 我得走了
We'll celebrate next week. Scott, I gotta go.
男性 30岁左右 大腿边有一个枪伤
Male, 30s. Single g.S.W. To proximal thigh.
校对：elsa 17 爱吃 慕斯
血压稳定 我们在阿拉莫那群人的队伍里发现他的
B.P.'S stable. We found him at the alamo.
我在哪儿 发生了什么
Where am I? What's happening?!
你中枪了 知道了么 但是我们会照看好你的
You've been shot, okay? But we're gonna take care of you.
嗨 能告诉我你的名字么
Hey, can you tell me your name?
后期：hhjie
我不知道 我不知道
I don't know. I don't know!
没有身份证 好像从别的星球冒出来的一样
No I.D. Guy's on another planet.
我们好不容易才把他拖进救护车
We could barely get him in the ambulance.
这里还有个问题 他是基督教科学家
There's another problem. He's a Christian scientist.
上面写着不要医治他
It says not to treat him.
时间轴：阿黎
我们在路上才注意到的
We didn't see it until we were en route.
我们不能治疗他 对么
We can't treat him, right?
我们得得到许可 否则就会被上诉的
We need consent or we'll get sued.
不用担心这个
Don't worry about it.
总监：慕斯
这个男的看上去像被炮弹击中一样
This guy looks like he was shot with a Cannon.
步枪 额 我在网上买的
Musket. Uh, I bought it online.
嘿 嘿 把那东西放下
Hey! Hey! Put that thing down!
嘿 我 我不知道它是上膛的 我真的不知道
Hey, I-I didn't know it was loaded, I swear.
听着 那个家伙把它丢在我手上的
Look, the dude lost it on me.
他袭击我的时候抢过枪 就像真的打仗一样
He attacked me and grabbed it like we were in a real fight,
然后枪走火了
and-and it went off.
你不能过来
You cannot be back here.
好吧 能有人查看一下我的肩膀吗
Okay, but can someone check on my arm?
好吧 等一下 你们把我带到哪儿了
Okay, wait, where are you taking me?
我们做什么 不 不
What do we got? No! No!
步枪伤口 1830年的阿拉莫之战特典
Musket wound. 1830s alamo special.
住手 住手 而且还是个非常焦躁的伤患
Stop it! Stop it! And one very agitated patient.
三 别碰我
...three! Don't touch me!
哇哦 哇哦 哇哦 哇哦 冷静一下
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! Calm down!
啊 冷静下来 我们在努力帮助你 冷静下来
Aah! Calm down! We're trying to help you! Calm down!
住手 我不需要 不 我们只是想帮帮你
Stop it! I don't -- no! We're trying to help!
给我两支安定剂
Get me 2 of ativan I.M.
还有谁去叫一下德 拉 科鲁兹医生
And somebody page Dr. De LA Cruz!
我们在帮助你 给我 给我走开
We're trying to help you. Get -- get off me!
乔丹 准备好注射安定剂了么
Jordan ready with the ativan.
好了 你们是要杀了我
Got it. You're trying to kill me!
谁去拿一下止血带 好吗
Somebody grab the hard restraints, yeah?
今晚可真算是地狱啊 德鲁真幸运请了假演习去了
Hell of a night for drew to be off on maneuvers.
我们要是可以用他的那些肌肉力气就好了
We could use the muscle.
是啊 他最好明天回来
Yeah. Be good to have him back tomorrow.
说实话
I gotta be honest.
我一点也不喜欢夜晚渗透战演习
I got no love for night infiltration exercise.
这可是小菜一碟 杰伊
This is a cakewalk, javy.
军队后备军可比不上
Army reserves is nothing compared to the 61 days
那61天在特种部队突击队的地狱训练
of hell in training school for rangers.
你还打算报名么 德鲁
You still thinking of signing up, drew?
我还没决定 我有个在医院里工作的伙计
I don't know. I've got a buddy
是个前突击队员
at the hospital I work with who's ex-ranger.
他说他可以帮我美言几句
He says he can put in a good word for me,
但是现在我比较注重医疗
but right now I'm more focused on medicine.
我猜你应该是更注重那些护士吧
Bet you're more focused on the nurses.
急症室从不缺辣妹
No lack of hotties in the E.R.
那么 杰伊 怎么样 恩
So, javy, what's the deal, huh?
第15团最终没能击败那些老古董么
15k march at the end too tough on the old bones?
噢 是的 伙计 那可跟你
Oh, yeah, dude, that might have something to do
整天坐在巡逻车上 不挪挪你懒散的屁股有关
with sitting on your lazy ass in a patrol car all day.
嘿 我老婆可喜欢我懒散的屁股
Hey, my wife loves my lazy ass,
所以一切顺利 你知道为什么吗
so it's all good. You know why?
因为那正好配她肥硕的臀部
'Cause that just matches her fat ass.
嘿 那可是孩子他妈
Hey, that's the mother of my children.
我喜欢她臀部的弧线
I like 'em curvy.
不是么 德鲁 噢 当然
Don't you, drew? Oh, yeah.
不 我 爱上我的摩托艇吧
No, me? Love me the motorboat.
就 在那儿
Just... Right in there.
赶快开始吧
Let's get moving.
我们只剩八个小时到达集合点
We only have eight hours to the rendezvous point.
然后德鲁就可以回到他的护士那儿了
And then drew can get back to those nurses of his.
我们走快点 这样可以给你换个衣服
Let's try moving a little faster so we can get you a robe.
你有那些上周无意留下的
Do you have the paperwork on those
患者信息么
involuntary hold patients from last week?
有 就在我桌子上的文件夹里
Yeah, it's in a folder on my desk.
呼叫拉戈萨医生
Paging Mr. Ragosa
请前往护士中心
to the nurses' station.
拉戈萨医生 请去护士中心报道
Mr. Ragosa, please report to the nurses' station.
我们来看看这个大家伙怎么了
Let's see what's going on with this big guy
他现在晕过去了
now that he's out.
里面至少有20个碎片
There must be 20 fragments in here.
远端血液流动还不错
Distal blood flow is good.
我们得把所有碎片一个个拿出来
We need to get every one of those out.
血压和脉搏下降
Blood pressure and pulse ox are dropping. Yeah, yeah.
大右心劳损
Massive right heart strain.
肯定是有弹片造成了阻塞
Piece of the bullet must have embolized.
呃 血压降到了40
Uh, b.P.'S down to 40.
我们必须立马从肺部取出弹片
We need to get that bullet out of the lung now!
乔丹
Jordan?
我刚刚跟一名护理人员谈了一下
I just talked to one of the paramedics,
他说这个人
and he said this guy came in
带着请勿医治的链子
with a "Do not treat" Bracelet on his wrist,
你们是不是忽略了这一点 -注射加入1%肾上腺素的利多
and that you ignored it. Lido with epi 1%.
开胸盘 -你如果这么做了
Open up a chest tray. If you did do that,
那么你就给你自己和医院招来了
you have opened yourself and this hospital up
一个不得了的官司 所以求你别这样
to a major lawsuit, so please,
拜托你向我保证你不会对他手术
please tell me you didn't do that.
那人骗你的 这里没有链子
The guy's lying. There's no bracelet.
乔丹
Jordan?
他戴了 我摘掉了
He had one. I cut it off.
噢 乔丹
Oh...Jordan.
就算她不摘下我也会摘掉手铐的
And even she didn't, I would have.
他快死了 他需要医治
He was dying. He needed to be treated.
我知道不能见死不救
I agree with you.
但我们要先把他确认为无自理能力的病人
But we get him declared incompetent first,
通过法律途径
contact legal.
我们不能就这样摘掉手铐
We don't just cut things off.
很抱歉 但我得要求你离开
Sorry, but I'm gonna need you to step back
让t.c来处理这个病人
and let t.C. Finish this patient.
你正式退出这场手术
You are officially suspended.
你知道么 我希望你们几个二货中有个变成辣妹
You know, I wish one of you fools was a hot chick.
现在有一个小小的视觉盛宴多好
A little eye candy would be nice right about now.
你什么意思额 兄弟
What do you mean, man?
我们是德克萨斯州看着最顺眼的战斗支援队了
This is the best-looking combat support team in Texas!
没错 是的
That's right. Yeah, right.
嘿 你们听说过C公司的那个基佬么
Hey, did you guys hear about that gay dude in "C" Company?
是有谣言 管他呢 谁在乎
Heard a rumor. Who cares?
我在乎 我想你
I do. I thought your
这一代应该更开放一些
generation was supposed to be more open-minded.
好吧 听着 有可能会
All right, look. I'm getting shot at
在叙利亚或伊拉克之类的什么地方中弹 对吧
by some sniper in Syria or Iraq or wherever, all right?
我可不希望掩护我的人
I don't need the guy who's supposed to be covering my ass
反而给我收尸
checking it out instead.
是的 我确定他就是这么想的
Yes, and I'm sure that's what he's thinking.
我现在可能会死在外面 但是 伙计
"I could die out here right now, but, man!
看看查理那骨瘦如柴的小屁屁
Look at that scrawny, pimply ass on Charlie!"
噢 是哒 -我是谁说说我的想法啊喂
Oh, yeah! Just my opinion, man.
现在 我要来射点什么了
And now I'm-a go shoot something!
嘿
Hey!
查理 别闹
Charlie, come on!
你在军队里无需做直男
You don't have to be straight to be in the army.
你只需保证笔直向前射击就好
You just have to shoot straight!
我就是这么想的 伙计 杰伊
That's all I care about, man! Javy!
小心 噢
Watch out! Oh!
就是说她救人得了个罐头
so she saves a life and she gets canned?
没人要解雇她
Nobody is firing her.
天呐 这里怎么这么热
God, why is it so hot in here?
我说过了
Like I said,
没人要解雇她
nobody is firing her.
她依旧有管理权
She's on administrative duty.
有备无患 我是在保护她
I'm taking this precaution to protect her
从长远来讲
from any further action.
我们先把他确定为无自理能力的病人 让他离开
We'll get him declared incompetent and go from there.
所以呢 我呆坐整晚么
So, what, I just sit around all night?
你 你得远离那个病人
You...Need to stay away from this patient,
还要交个该死的报告并且希望
and you need to talk to legal and hope to hell
他们认定他没有自理能力
they do find him incompetent.
这之后 无论你对病人做什么
After that, whatever you do with any other patients,
别告诉我就好
I don't want to know about it.
现在如果你有空 我真的好想喝水 去倒杯来
Now if you'll excuse me, I really need a glass of water.
会没事的 你不明白
It'll be okay. You don't know that.
我不像你一样有些位高权重的朋友
I don't have your friends in high places.
抱歉我这么说你的朋友
Sorry I put you guys in this position.
嘿 怎么了
Hey, what's going on?
我从没见过乔丹这样子
I've never seen Jordan act like that before.
说来话长
It's a long story.
让我们把剩下的弹壳取出来吧
Let's get the rest of this shrapnel.
哈维 -好的 我来了
Javy -yeah. I'm coming
啊 我的肩膀 我的肩膀拉不出来
aah! My shoulder! I can barely pull him out.
好的 没事 做你能做的 好嘛 啊
Yeah, just sack up, do what you can, okay? Aah!
啊
Aah!
噢
Ohh!
噢 天呐
Oh, God.
好了 没事 我先去检查哈维
Here. Okay. I'm gonna go check on javy.
你怎么了 我们怎么了
What do we got? What do we got?
噢 我的肩膀
Oh! My shoulder.
噢 很疼的
Oh! That really hurts!
你的肩膀交接点有一处脱臼
You got a separation of an A.C. Joint.
德鲁 德鲁 我需要你
Drew! Drew, I need you!
我来了 我马上来 米奇
I'm coming. I'm gonna be right there, Mikey.
快来 德鲁 快来 德鲁
Come on, drew. Come on. Drew!
我已经是最快了
I'm going as fast as I can.
我的脚腕折断了
My ankle's screwed up!
好疼
I'm in pain.
撑住 米奇 撑住啊
Hang in there, Mikey, hang in there.
你没事了 我现在去看看米奇 -好的
You're good. Now I need to go to Mikey. Yeah.
等等 等等 等等 查理在哪
Wait, wait, wait. Where's Charlie?
查理 查理
Charlie! Charlie!
查理
Charlie!
哈维 我知道你很疼 你去找查理
Javy, I know you're hurting. You gotta go find Charlie.
好的 快去吧
Okay. Go.
好了 米奇 我来了 我来了
Okay, Mikey, I'm here, I'm here!
查理
Charlie!
嘿 那个疯子快死了么
Hey, is that crazy dude gonna die?
嘿 你别动啊 先生
Hey just hold still, sir.
我 我不知道
And I-I don't know.
我不想坐牢 我什么都没做啊
I can't go to jail. I'd never make it there.
我看过每一集OZ
I saw every episode of "Oz."
他们生吃活人 是的 他们吃人
They eat guys like me alive. Yeah, they would.
但我觉得你很安全 那个人他
But I think you're safe. That guy is
很明显他的情况不稳定
it's pretty clear he's unstable.
哇嗷 呃 圣诞安娜 对嘛
Whoa. Uh, general Santa Anna, right?
多好看的戏服
Sweet costume. It's...
有我打伤的那人的消息么
Any news on the guy I shot?
有的 他们  他们把他麻醉了 在一号手术室
Yeah, they they've got him sedated in trauma 1.
候诊室里挤满了来复诊的人
The waiting room is filling up again with reenactors,
我们还给一些醉鬼吊盐水袋
and we hooked up some more drunks to the saline packs.
还有 呃 还把食物中毒的人送回了家
And, uh, sent three food poisoning guys home, too.
啊 因为那盘脏兮兮的炖兔肉
Ah. That rabbit stew's nasty.
呃 我才和那个墨西哥佬打架的
Uh, that's why I fight on the Mexican side.
我们有一个快餐车
We have a food truck.
没错 你们还有
All right, you guys only have
一对病人需要照看
a couple dozen more patients to go.
我尽快结束工作后过来 好么
I'll join you as soon as I'm finished, okay?
我还会向你们示范一次劲外静脉注射
And I'll let you watch me do one of the E.J.S.
我等医生等了两个小时了
I've been waiting for two hours to see a doctor.
我 我知道 女士 我很抱歉
I-I know, ma'am. Look, I am so sorry.
那些复诊的人忙得我们没有空闲的医生来看病
The alamo reenactors have us slammed with patients.
我的胃疼死了
My stomach's killing me.
呃 我会尽力快点为你叫来医生的
Uh...I'll get you a doctor as soon as I can.
嘿 嘿
Hey. Hey.
你为2号测试室要了快军用板
You ordered a g.I. Panel on exam 2,
但我在那没看到病人
but haven't seen the patient yet.
她有麻烦么 -是的 我知道 我看到表了
She's pissed. Yeah, I-I know. I read the chart.
呃 好像是胃受凉之类的
Uh, it sounds like stomach flu or something. Um...
噢 但托佛会做一个劲外静脉注射
Oh, but Topher's gonna do an external jugular,
我很想去看看 我以前没见过
and I really wanna watch. I've never seen one, so...
但是她的测试结果已经出来了
But her results are already back.
好吧 我看完劲外静脉注射就去看看她
Great. I will see her after the e.J.
嗯 先开点点滴好么 谢谢
Um, just start some fluids, okay? Thanks.
调度 是的 是的 我是卡拉汉医生
Dispatch? Yeah, yeah, this is Dr. Callahan.
呃 这有一个护理员叫冈萨雷斯
Um, there was a paramedic Gonzalez
他从30号白杨林里带来了一个有枪伤的病人
he came in with a G.S.W. From the alamo
就在今晚
30 tonight.
呃 你能叫他到急诊室来么
Um, can you tell him to come by the E.R.?
我有一些消息他可能需要知道
I have some info that he may need.
德鲁 是不是断了
Drew! Is it -- is it broken?
是脱臼 没事 我会让它复位的 好么
And dislocated. Okay, I'm gonna try and get your boot off, okay?
啊 啊 好的
Aah! Aah! Okay --
好的 米奇 我找到点了 准备好
okay, Mikey, I just gotta get in there, okay?
我找到了 很好 我用我的手指
I got you -- that's right. Let me get my finger --
啊
aah!
麦基 我摸不到你血管的跳动
Mikey, I can't feel a pulse.
你知道吗 这说明脱臼切断了
Okay? Means the dislocation's cutting off
往你脚部的供血
the blood flow to your foot,
所以我要控制一下你的断骨
so I've gotta reduce the fracture.
那是个什么意思
What the hell does that mean?
就是说大概会疼得让你哭爹喊娘
Means it's gonna hurt like a son of a bitch.
好的 深呼吸 好的
Okay, deep breath. Okay.
好吗 倒数三下
Okay? Count of three.
听见了吗 一 二
You with me? One, two...
啊
Aah!
德鲁我干你大爷 啊
Damn you, drew! Aah!
总比直接去死强吧 好吗
It's better than dying. All right?
杰伊在哪儿
Where is javy?
我看到你的后颈在滴血
There's blood dripping down the back of your neck.
什么
What?
滴血
There is?
是 的确有 好吧
Yes, there is. Okay. Um...
现在轮到你来折磨我了 麦基
You're about to get even, Mikey.
这是个皮肤缝合器
It's a skin stapler.
好吗 它用起来非常方便
All right? It's self-explanatory.
把伤口的两边推到一起
Push the edges of the wound together.
用点力
Apply pressure.
按一下按钮
Squeeze the trigger.
好的 就是这样 嗯 嗯
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
噢
Ow!
德鲁 德鲁
Drew! Drew!
我找到查理了 但是他情况非常不好
I found Charlie. He's in really bad shape.
我们先去找查理 马上就回来
We're gonna get Charlie. Be right back.
你要坚持住 好吗
You hold on, okay?
那时候你在阿拉莫 你被人射中了
You were at the alamo. You were shot.
他失去意识了 是吗
He's incompetent, right?
他的麻醉效果还没完全消除
He's still too out of it from the anesthesia
所以我还不能下定论 嗯
for me to make a diagnosis. Mm-hmm.
我觉得我该查一查 毕竟乔丹呼了我整整三次
I just thought I'd check since Jordan had paged me three times.
唔 到底是怎么了
Mm-hmm. What's going on?
他是个信基督教的科学家
He's a Christian scientist.
他被送来的时候 手上还带着请勿医治的链子
He came in with a "Do not treat" Bracelet.
-乔丹把它卸下来了 -什么
-Jordan cut it off. -What?
是啊 所以如果你宣布他失去意识的话
Yeah. So you declaring him incompetent --
可算是帮了她大忙了
go a long way towards getting her off the hook.
好吧 首先 我真不敢相信她那么做了
Well, first of all, I can't believe she did that.
但是我也不会空口无凭地就给他盖个戳
But I'm not just gonna label him without talking.
他之前大喊大叫了
He was screaming, he was yelling --
那不能说明他就真的神志不清了
that could be for any number of a hundred things.
你知道的 我很喜欢乔丹 但是我不会冒着被吊销行医执照
Look, I like Jordan, but I'm not gonna risk my license
或是被安上个玩忽职守的罪名的风险 就毫无根据地诊断
or a malpractice suit by giving an unwarranted diagnosis,
尤其是在她还干了这种蠢事的时候
especially when she does something that stupid.
如果换作是我 我也会做同样的决定的
I would have done the same thing.
你想让我说些什么 TC
What do you want me to say here, t.C.?
关于这个我不同意你的观点
I don't agree with you on this,
所以我们还是别讨论这个话题了
so let's just not talk about it.
他醒了 我去进行诊断
He wakes up, I'll make the diagnosis.
但是可别对我指手画脚
But don't tell me how to do my job.
你是对的
You're right.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
戴维斯护士
Nurse Davis,
请到理疗科报到
please report to physical therapy.
戴维斯护士 请到理疗科来
Nurse Davis, physical therapy.
亚历山大医生 请到法务部报到
Dr. Alexander, report to the legal department.
一切都会好起来的
Everything's gonna be okay.
那看起来不太好
That doesn't look good.
他需要去手术室
He needs an O.R.
呼叫作战中心 去找救援直升机来
Call the t.O.C. And get a medevac!
我们滚动的时候天线掉了下来
The antenna tore off when we rolled.
收音机被击中了 这里完全没有手机信号
Radio's shot. And there's no cell signal out here.
我们只能靠自己了 德鲁 我来包扎止血
We're on our own, drew. I'll try to tamponade the bleeding,
但是这个这是应急用的
but this packing's just a temporary fix.
去把担架拿过来 我们要去撤离点
Get the litter. We got to get up to the extraction point.
撤离点离这里有5英里 所以 嗯 我们最好现在就动身
It's at least 5 Miles. Well, then we better get going.
好的
Okay.
莫莉说 他在那里
Mollie says he's been
已经站了整整5分钟了
standing there for the past five minutes.
我猜他大概是打算想个法子
I figure he's trying to find a way
来减轻我们的电耗费用
to save money on electricity.
嘿
Hey.
迈克尔
Michael?
我从你的阿司匹林药瓶里拿了几片
I took a couple of pills from your aspirin bottle,
但是我现在百分之五百地确定它们不是阿司匹林
but I'm pretty sure they weren't aspirin.
你能告诉我那是什么吗
You wanna tell me what it was?
-你是说 从我桌上的那个瓶子里拿的吗 -是
-From the bottle on my desk? -Yes.
那是 呃 摇头丸
They were, um... M.D.M.A.
摇头丸
M.D.M.A.?
就是那种会致幻的
As in ecstasy?
-你怎么会有 -我很抱歉
-Why do you have -- -I’m so sorry.
我保证会给你一个合理的解释
I swear there is a legitimate explanation.
所以我会怎么样
What's happening to me?
好的 呃 你的 你的感官会变得异常敏锐
Well, um, your -- your senses are heightening,
你会变得更开放 也会倾向于和人
and you will be more open and physical
身体接触 呃 和其他东西也是
with people...And objects.
不 不 不不不
No. No, no, no, no, no.
这不科学
This is not happening.
我能战胜它
I can fight this.
实际上你完全没办法控制这种情况的发生
You don't really have control over it.
我觉得你最好就待在你的办公室里
Maybe you should just sit in your office
直到药效过去
until it passes.
我现在对你火冒三丈
I am so angry with you right now.
你们这些女人今天晚上把我整惨了
You women are really messing up my night.
我们日后算账
We're gonna deal with this later.
没问题 多喝点水
Okay. Drink a lot of water.
喝水
Water.
啊 拉戈萨嗑药了
Uh, ragosa's on ecstasy?
嘘 没有 怎么说
Shh! No, how --
呃 听着
I -- wait.
我正在做一个实验研究
So I was involved in an experimental study...
是关于摇头丸在
On the effects of m.D.M.A.
患有创伤后应激障碍的士兵身上的药效的 而这个药 可以
On soldiers with p.T.S.D., and the drug, it just --
它会产生血清素和催产素
it releases serotonin and oxytocin
这样士兵们的创伤得以减轻
so the soldiers can relive their trauma
也不会感到任何痛苦
without feeling pain.
好吧
Okay.
拜托别说出去
Please keep this on the d.L.
我懂的 我懂的
Gotcha. Got it. Gotcha. Gotcha.
麦基在那儿会没事的
Mikey's gonna be fine back there.
杰伊 我知道你的肩膀痛得要死
And I know your shoulder's killing you, javy,
但你得尽量跟上我
but you gotta keep up with me.
-查理的状况刻不容缓 -是啊 我尽力了
-Charlie is in bad shape. -I’m trying, man.
你觉得他能挺过去吗
You think he's gonna make it?
我不知道
I don't know.
他不能就这么去死 他还是个孩子
He can't die, man. He's just a kid.
我见过不少孩子丧命了
I've seen a lot of kids die.
年轻在死亡面前 完全算不了什么
Age has got nothing to do with it.
我想说的是 德鲁
I gotta tell you, drew --
我想退出所有这一切跟军队有关系的事
I want to quit this whole army thing.
我才加入了后备军 想要
I just joined the reserves to get some extra cash
为我的妻儿多挣点外快
for my wife and kids.
但是我还不想死
I don't want to get killed.
你呢 难道你不怕死吗
Aren't you afraid of getting killed?
没有人想送死 杰伊
No one wants to die, javy,
但是如果我在工作时总想着那些
but if I think about that out there,
我就没办法好好完成一个医务兵的任务
I'm not gonna be able to do my job as a medic.
我们为什么停下来了
Why are we stopping?
杰伊 我们进入射程了
Javy, we're on the range.
他们的射程 快跑
The shooting range! Go!
跑 快跑 快 快点
Go, go, go! Move, move, move!
趴下来
Get down!
卧槽 我要杀了他们
Damn it! I'm gonna kill them!
他妈的 我们要冲出去
Let's get the hell outta here!
莫莉 我想知道
Mollie, I need to see if anyone filled out
有没有人为那个无名氏填了失踪人员报告
a missing person report on John Doe.
-你能打去圣安东尼奥警署问问吗 -我现在就去
-Can you call s.A.P.D.? -I’m on it.
别找警署可能比较好
Maybe we shouldn't call s.A.P.D.
处理无名氏的时候我们总是这么办的
We always do that with John does.
我们不知道他的病史或精神病史
We have no idea what his medical or psychiatric history is.
他的家人可能正在找他
His family could be looking for him.
他的家人 很有可能
His family, more likely than not,
会对他不管不顾 任由他丧命
are the ones that would let him die.
你可不知道真实情况
You don't know that.
他们是信基督教的科学家
They're Christian scientists,
也就是说 他们可能会试图阻止
which means they are gonna want to stop
所有我们准备采取的治疗方法
any treatment that you or I want to do,
病人会很痛苦的
and that man will needlessly suffer.
让我只做好本职工作行吗
Just let me do my job, okay?
不要因为你搞砸了还剪了他的链子
Don't get all pissy at me because you screwed up
就对我发火
and cut off his bracelet.
他就要死了 好的 他一心求死
He was dying. Yeah, that's what he wanted.
所以他才会带上链子
That's why he wore the bracelet.
这是他的选择
That's his choice.
在可以治好的情况下求死
To die when he can easily be saved?
你支持这个选择吗
You're backing that?
我支持个人自由
I am backing personal freedom.
我支持每个人对自己的身体有决定权
I'm backing nobody telling anybody
不需要听从别人
what they can do with their body.
我会这么做吗
Would I ever do that?
不 我相信他有权这么想
No, but I believe in his right to belive in it.
他可能都不知道他信仰的是什么
He may not know what he believes.
可你在剪手环的时候也不知道啊
You didn't know that when you cut it off.
你都看到了他的意愿 还是一意孤行
You saw his religion, and you made a choice.
也许他没有辨别能力 但如果他不是呢
Maybe that guy is incompetent, but what if he wasn't?
如果他只是个律师
What if he was just a lawyer
和你有着不同的想法呢
who had a different belief than yours?
你还会这么做吗
Would you still do it?
只要送进医院我就会救
Every single time they're brought in here.
那我想我们只是看法不同罢了
Well, then I guess we just see things differently.
很多事情都如此
On a lot of things.
-你什么意思 -没什么
-What does that mean? -Forget it.
不 你说出来
No, say it.
好吧
Okay.
我是说 我知道你和TC在交往
It means that I know you're sleeping with T.C.
这没什么 又不关我的事
And that's fine. It's not my business.
但我不敢相信的是 在我们聊天之后
But I can't believe after some of the conversations
谈到了我和他 还有我们过去的恋情
that you and I have had about me, him, and our past,
你从来都没想过你该和我说一声
that you never once thought that maybe you should mention it.
我这儿需要个医生
I need a doctor in here.
胸好痛 我都不能呼吸了 -别急
-My chest! I can't breathe. -Okay.
-心率只有30多下 -好的
-Heart rate's in the 30s. -All right.
没事 别急
Okay. Okay.
我要听一下你的心率
I'm gonna listen to your heart.
她的心脏S-T段抬高
There are s.T. Elevations.
她心脏病发作了
This woman's having a heart attack.
-为什么没人给她看病 -我以为她看过了
-Why hasn't she been seen? -I thought she had.
呼叫心脏病室
Page cardiology.
给我325毫克阿司匹林
Give me 325 milligrams of aspirin
再给我那个心脏起搏器
and grab the pacer pads.
-还需要做一个正规的心电图 现在就要 -她有过了
-We need a formal E.K.G. Now. -She already had one.
谁给她弄的
Well, who ordered it?
-怎么回事 她是你的病人吗
What happened? Is this your patient?
是啊 她得了肠胃炎
Uh, yeah. She had the stomach flu.
那你就给她做了个心电图
And did you order an E.K.G. on her?
我以为只是常规性的
I-I did as part of a g.I. Work-up.
你看了吗
Did you look at it?
这个病人是个40多岁的非洲裔
You have an African-American woman in her late 40s
有糖尿病 还一直胃痛
with diabetes complaining about stomach pain,
你为什么不看看她的心电图呢
and you didn't look at her E.K.G.?
她应该两个小时前就在实验室治疗了
She should have been in the cath lab two hours ago.
但是 她没有说她还胸痛啊
Look -- she wasn't complaining o-of chest pain.
这不是理由 如果你做了测试
It doesn't matter. If you order a test,
你就要为结果负责
you're responsible for the results,
如果是做心电图 你一定要立即看有没有问题
and if that test is an E.K.G., you look at it immediately.
下壁心肌梗死
Inferior m.I.
保罗 你是个急诊医生 你的工作就是
Paul, you're an E.R. Doctor. Your job is to think of things
要想到病人最有可能得什么病
that would kill your patient first
然后让病情平缓下来
and label it as benign later.
不是速度快就万事大吉了
It isn't all about the flashy procedures.
-抱歉 -别向我道歉
-I'm sorry. -Don't apologize to me.
学习 下次做得更好
Learn. Do better.
我告诉过你要看检查结果的
I told you to look at the tests, man.
我想给你个提醒
I want to give you the heads-up. Mm-hmm.
乔丹知道我们的事了
Jordan knows about us.
-她怎么知道的 -我不清楚
-How? -I don't know.
我们在为一个病人争执
We were arguing about John Doe.
多大的事啊 我们各执己见
Big deal. We see it differently.
然后 然后她就说了这话
And then it just... Came out.
好吧
Right.
你想让我和她谈谈吗
You want me to talk to her?
不用 我自己就能应对
No, I can fight my own battles.
除去今晚 她确实有理由对我发火
Aside from tonight, she has every right to be pissed at me.
我们是朋友 你又是她前男友
We were becoming friends. You're her ex.
我应该告诉她的
I should have told her.
TC 冈萨雷斯医护要见你
T.C., paramedic Gonzalez is here to see you.
那个病人情况稳定了吗
Is John Doe ready?
是 他病情已经控制住了
Yeah, he's coherent now.
嘿 伙计 谢谢你能来
Hey, buddy. Thanks for coming by.
我的工会代表说我不应该和你谈话
My union rep said I shouldn't talk to you.
得了吧 你的工会代表就是个蠢蛋
Nah, your union rep's a douche.
他想我们一样在一线工作嘛 又不是
Is he on the front lines like you and me? No.
我们来谈谈你到底看到了什么
Let's talk about what you really saw.
我要对你的智力做个评估
I have to determine your competency,
我需要你集中精力 仔细想想
so I need you to focus and think really hard.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
我不知道 我不知道我是谁
I don't know. I-I don't know who I am.
求你救救我
Please help me. Please.
你放心 我会帮助你的
That's right, I'm gonna help you.
我会给你看几幅图
I'm going to show you some pictures.
这个测试有助于你恢复记忆
It's a test to help you remember.
只要感觉熟悉就告诉我
Let me know if anything seems familiar.
不论多小的事都行
It doesn't matter if it's the smallest thing.
想起什么了么
Anything?
没有
No.
等等 回去前面一幅
Wait, wait. Go back.
这幅图让你想到什么了
What does this make you think of?
-一个小吃店 -很好
-A diner. -Good.
你喜欢路边摊
You like diners?
是啊 我想我是在一个小吃店 在那儿吃东西
Yeah, I-I think I ate there, at a diner.
还有什么吗
Anything else?
克莉丝 克莉丝汀
Chris...Christine.
你想起了一个叫克莉丝汀的人
You remember someone named Christine?
是啊 克莉丝汀
Yeah, Christine.
呃 但 但我不记得她长什么样子
Uh...But I-I don't remember what she looks like
不记得她是谁
or who she is.
其他什么都不记得了
I don't remember anything else.
为什么我会这样
Oh...Why is this happening to me?
我是谁
Who am I?
我知道这难以置信 但我们会弄清楚的
I know it's scary, but we're gonna figure this out,
我们会弄清楚是谁在找你 我保证
and we'll find whoever's looking for you, I promise.
行了
All right.
一切安全 行动起来
All clear. Let's move.
查理又流血了
Charlie's bleeding again.
艹
Damn it.
怎么了
What's happening?
肠子有一截爆了
Part of the bowel has ruptured.
一会儿要给他缝上
I gotta suture it up later.
这就是你不想当突击队员的原因吗
This is why you're not going for ranger, right?
这不值得
It's not worth it.
我们可能丧命 为了什么
We can be killed, and for what?
就为了保护个该死的领导吗
Protecting some damn dictator?
这个傻孩子 他是个蠢蛋
This stupid kid -- he's an idiot.
如果他不开启就不会被伤的这么重
He wouldn't be hurt so bad if he wasn't firing that stupid gun.
哈维 他能听到 闭嘴
Javy, he can hear you. Shut up.
现在不是埋怨的时候
Now is not the time.
克莉丝汀也像你一样是个阿拉莫战争重演者吗
Is Christine an alamo reenactor like you?
医生
Doctor.
社会主义工人党的失踪人口中
S.A.P.D. Doesn't have a missing person
没有符合这个病人的资料
fitting John Doe's description.
然后我就给基督教科学教堂留了信息
And I left messages at the Christian science church.
很好
Good.
他刚刚想起了一个小吃店和一个叫克莉丝汀的女孩
He just mentioned a diner and a girl named Christine.
要么他带她在那儿约会过 要么她在那儿工作
Either he took her on a date there once, or she works there.
我希望是后者 你能
I'm hoping it's the latter. Can you --
给附近的全天营业小吃店打电话是吧
call all the 24-hour diners in the area?
我会帮你一起的 大概有多少
I'll help. How many can there be?
叫TC来
Get t.C.
TC
T.C.!
怎么了
What happened?
他之前还好好的 突然一下
He was fine, then all of a sudden
他的生命起搏器就叫个不停
his vitals started going crazy.
也许肺部又被堵住了
Maybe it's another embolus to the lung.
不会的 我把所有弹片都取出了
No, I got rid of all the shrapnel.
肯定是其他的东西 注射150毫克胺碘酮
Must be something else. Push 150 milligrams amiodarone.
准备好了
On it.
等等 太迟了 看他的血压
No, wait. It's too late. Look at his blood pressure.
除颤了
Clear.
调回窦性节律
Back in a sinus rhythm.
血压增加到105
Pressure's up to 105.
这到底怎么回事
What the hell was that?
我也不清楚
I have no idea.
可能一个小时左右
She's probably not going to wake up
她都醒不了 医生
for another hour or so, doctor.
没事
That's all right.
我在这等着她醒过来就行
I'll just sit with her until she does.
他要做个胸部CT
Okay, so we need a stat chest C.T.
还有毒理检查
And add on a tox panel.
-谢谢 -马上就好
Thank you. Right away.
真是千钧一发
That was close. So...
他在出问题之前你知道什么了没
What did you learn before he started to code?
像是神经导致的游离状态
Looks like a mania-induced fugue state.
他本身应该记忆衰退
Based on the retrograde amnesia,
他的战争重演倾向严重
his aggressive behavior towards the reenactors --
所以这个病例更复杂
so this case is even more complicated.
目前看是的 这个情况很复杂
For now. It's a tricky condition.
诱因非常的多
It could be caused by any number of things.
可能持续数小时甚至几个月
Could last for hours or even months.
我们需要知道他是谁
We need to find out who he is.
我知道这帮不了乔丹
And I know that doesn't help Jordan.
如果他有家人 是会上诉的
If he does have family that could sue --
不 相信我 乔丹更关心这个人的安危
no, trust me, Jordan cares more about this guy living
而不是自己身陷什么麻烦
than any trouble she's in.
但如果他们因此解雇她 我也辞职
But if they try to can her for it, I'll quit.
这样就会引起董事会的注意
That will get the board's attention.
你真的会为此辞职
You'd really quit?
真是够义气
That's very loyal.
我去实验室看看
I'm gonna go check on the labs,
看能不能有所帮助
see if there's anything I missed.
哟 哟 托尼 你好啊
Yo, yo, what up, Tony?
嘿 托佛医生
Hey, Dr. Topher.
我们今晚可是有特别推荐
We got a great special tonight.
-看看这个 -我看到了
Check it out. I see what you did there.
你想听听我对你的输精管切除术的想法吗
You want my advice on your vasectomy?
是啊 我还真是觉得难以启齿啊
Yeah, I was just too shy to ask.
还是汉堡和薯条 托尼 快做吧
Just a burger and fries, Tony. Let's go.
嘿 托佛 嘿
Hey, Topher. Hey!
今晚真是糟透了 是吧
Hey. Is your crappy night still going crappy?
天啊 你真是哪壶不开提哪壶
Man, you sure do know what to say to a girl
-应该给我点正能量 知道吗 -天将降大任于斯人也
to cheer her up, you know that? Ah, it's a gift.
是啊
Yeah.
现在 你听着
Now, you know, uh,
如果律师问你 你会不会再这么做了
when the lawyers ask you if you'd do it again,
你要回答 不会了 记住吗
the answer is "No," Right?
记住了
Yeah.
我也许会处理的更好
I probably could have handled that better.
托佛医生
Dr. Topher.
嘿 给我杯咖啡好吗
Hey, can I get a coffee?
好的 给你
Yeah, you got it.
也许应该告诉你一声
I thought you might want to know,
我已经确定了那个病人的精神问题
I declared John Doe incompetent.
这不是什么难事
Wasn't rocket science.
我需要好好检查他 乔丹
I needed to examine him, Jordan.
你不会毫不检查就直接把我给你的诊断
You wouldn't rubber-stamp any diagnosis I gave
用胶布封了口吧
without checking.
听着 我知道我处理
Look, I know I didn't handle this whole thing
T.C.的这件事并不十分妥当
with t.C. Very well.
我应该提前告诉你的
I should have said something to you.
是啊 你应该告诉我的 考虑到
Yeah, you probably should have, considering
你之前有72个机会告诉我
that you had at least 72 chances to tell me
你在跟我的前男友上床
that you were sleeping with my ex.
你早应该告诉我
You could have told me before I set you up
在我邀请你参加那个相亲之前 我现在想想
on that blind date, which, in retrospect,
真奇怪你竟然去了
is totally bizarre that you went.
我希望能更了解你
I wanted to get to know you better.
这就是我为什么去
That's why I went.
不管怎么说 T.C.和我都没有认真的对待这段感情
Anyway, t.C. And I aren't that serious.
兰德里 你和T.C.做了或是没做什么
Landry, what you and t.C. Do or don't do
我一点都不关心
is really not my concern.
现在你可是口不对心了 你说什么
Now you're being dishonest. Excuse me?
承认吧 你和你的前男友在同一家医院工作
Come on, you work in a hospital with your ex-boyfriend.
你很积极的想要安排他的排班
You actively pursued to manage his shift,
同时你的现男友还在达拉斯呢
all while your current boyfriend lives in Dallas.
是的 那也是斯科特工作的地方
Yeah. That's where Scott works.
乔丹 这是简单的心理学
Jordan, this is psych 101.
你并没有兴趣跟斯科特定下终生
You have no interest in really committing to Scott,
因为你还对前男友T.C.有感觉
because you still have feelings for ex-boyfriend t.C.
T.C.不仅仅是前男友好吗
T.C. Isn't just an ex-boyfriend, okay?
他不是随便什么我约会过一会的男人
He isn't some guy that I dated for a little while
-这并不是这样的 -我明白 你们有一段情史
and it just didn't work out. I understand. You have history.
你不明白我们经历过什么
You have no idea what we have.
T.C.回家的时候很颓废
T.C. Was a wreck when he came home.
他不是你今天看到的样子
He wasn't the man that you see today.
我离开了我的工作 朋友 我的一切
I left my job, my friends, everything
这样我就可以回到这里 来帮助他走出困境
so that I could come here and help him out.
我 陪他走过了地狱
I...Stood by him through hell.
所以说 是的 我们有一段情史
So, yeah, we have a history,
而且 你说得对 我确实还对他有好感
and, yes, I have feelings for him.
吃薯条吗
Fries?
莫莉 你找到那个病人的克莉丝汀了吗
Mollie, you found John Doe's Christine?
喔噢噢噢噢
Whoo!
托佛
Topher!
这是我的果酱 是我的果酱
This is my jam! This is my jam!
好的
Okay.
医生
Doc?
我在这里 查理
I'm here, Charlie.
我不能再走下去了
I...Can't...G-go anymore.
好痛 快放下我
Hurts too much. Put me down.
好吧 杰伊 把他放下 说到三 来吧
Okay. Javy, put him down. Count of three. All right.
一 二 三
One...Two...Three.
让我看看
Let me take a look.
嘿 你看上去很好 小伙子
Hey, you're looking great, man.
我跟你说 你看上去好极了
I'm telling you, you look spectacular.
我是认真的 我要放弃了
I'm serious. I give up.
我需要你振作下去 你懂吗
I need you to keep fighting. You understand me?
振作下去 你可以的 查理
Keep fighting. You can do it, Charlie.
好的
Okay.
数到三就抬起来
Up on the count of three.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
呃 啊 你抓住了吗
Uhh! Aah! You got it?
你还好吗 查理 感觉好吗
You all right there, Charlie? Doing okay?
我很好 抓紧 啊
I'm all right. Hold on. Ahh.
这里 好的
Here. Yeah.
好 好 好的 推一下
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Push.
我们一个小时内如果没办法把他运过去
We don't get him there in the next hour,
他就必死无疑
he's not gonna make it.
你要和他说话 分散他的注意力
You gotta keep him talking, distract him.
明白
Copy that.
好的
Okay.
数到三就抬起来
Up on three.
一 二 三
One, two, three!
你知道我不应该来治疗他的
You know I'm not supposed to be treating him.
嘿
Hey.
是的 好吧 我需要你帮我想想 好吗
Yeah, well, I need your brain, all right?
他的心肺器官都在摇晃 我找不到它们
His vitals went wonky. I can't figure it out.
胸透什么也没显示 好吗
Chest C.T. Came back with nothing, all right?
现在他在发烧
Now he's spiking a fever
他对抗生素也没有反应
and he isn't responding to antibiotics.
我觉得他的腿已经感染了 好的
I think the leg must be getting septic. Okay.
但是他已经打了两针抗生素了
But he's already on two antibiotics.
我加了第三个
I've added a third,
我也重新做了血液培养
I've resent his blood cultures, and --
他的体温在上升
his fever's climbing.
上降温措施 现在他又还是抽搐了
Cooling measures now. And now he's twitching.
这他妈的到底是怎么了 好吧 好吧 呃
What the hell's going on? Okay, okay, um...
可能是脑膜炎 或者是 子弹疮口引起的破伤风
It could be meningitis, or...Tetanus from the bullet.
是吗 可能吧 是肌肉张力障碍反应吗
Right? Maybe. Dystonic reaction?
是的 刚刚接到电话 是一个认识他的女人
Yes. Just got off the phone with a woman who knows him.
她说他三周前还好好的
And she said he was fine three weeks ago,
那么我想他的神游症
so I think his fugue state has to be connected
大概跟病情的恶化有关了 怎么有关
to his worsening condition. In what way?
我也不知道 兰德里 这是个医学问题
I'm not sure. Landry, this is a medical issue.
你有什么见解能帮到我们的
When you have something that can really help us,
告诉我们 谢谢
let us know. Thanks.
好的
Okay.
乔丹 乔丹 注射150毫升的胺碘酮
Jordan. Jordan! Push 150 milligrams amiodarone.
美国大学毕业生 你怎么了 疯了吗
Aggies over u.T.? What are you, crazy?
你还有什么好说的 哈维
What else you got, javy?
嘿 查理 如果你一打响指
Hey, Charlie, if you could snap your fingers
就能到任何地方的话 你想去哪 伙计
and be anywhere, where would you be, buddy?
我不知道 不 你知道的 伙计 说说吧
I don't know. Yeah, you do, man. Come on.
你想去哪儿 我想是维加斯吧
Where you wanna go? I'm thinking Vegas
陪陪姑娘 喝点儿小酒 怎么样
with all the chickies, a little bit of booze, huh?
在 在海湾那里 抓枪鱼
In -- in the Gulf, catching marlins.
我看不错 你呢 哈维
Love it. How about you, javy?
呃 迈阿密海滩吧 宝贝
Uh, Miami beach, baby.
跟我老婆一起在水池边上和玛格丽塔
Drinking margaritas with my wife by the pool,
让我父母代管孩子们一星期
have my parents take the kids for the week.
那就是个假期了 你呢
That'd be a vacation. How about you?
哦 伙计 我爱死老城市了
Oh, man, I love the old cities.
巴黎 罗马 什么的 它们的历史
You got Paris, Rome -- just the history of 'em,
学学它们的历史
learning about 'em.
是啊 我和瑞克 我们经常到夏威夷去
Yeah, me and Rick, we usually end up in Hawaii, though.
我 我的哥哥 瑞克
My-my brother -- Rick.
我经常和我哥哥一起度假
I vacation a lot with my brother.
我们很亲近
We're close.
夏威夷很好 是啊
Hawaii's cool. Yeah.
撑住 查理 撑住
Hang on, Charlie. Hang on.
拉戈萨先生 请汇报记录
Mr. Ragosa, please report to records.
这么积极
This positivity!
哦 伙计 就是这里
Oh, man, this is where it's at.
我觉得
I just feel really,
非常 非常 非常 好
really, really good!
肯尼告诉我拉戈萨不小心磕了点药
Kenny told me that ragosa accidentally took some e,
他就嗨了一整晚
and he's just been rolling all night.
你应该 你真应该回去工作了
You should -- you should really go back to work.
啊
Ahh!
-是的 对 -手术 是吗
- Yeah. Right. - Surgeon? Huh?
我看见你了 看见你了
I see you! I see you!
记住阿拉莫
Remember the alamo!
他的腰部刺穿和破伤风滴定量呈阴性
John Doe's lumbar puncture and tetanus titer are negative.
但他的发热体温还在上升
But his fever keeps going up.
他一直在痉挛
And he keeps spasming.
我们还有什么没想到的
What are we missing?
我都问了自己好几个小时了
Been asking myself for hours.
也许你不应该让兰德里走开
Maybe you shouldn't have jumped all over Landry.
这个时候讨论那件事好吗
Is now really the time to talk about that?
我只是在说救这个病人的事情
I'm talking about saving John Doe.
听着 我们不知道他哪里有问题
Look, we have no idea what's wrong with him.
她只是想帮忙
She was just trying to help.
通过背背理论吗
By throwing out theories?
呃 这也是我们正在做的
Well, that is what we are doing.
听着 我知道这晚上对你来说很不好受
Look, I know that it's been a rough night for you.
如果你想聊天
If you want to talk...
我知道你和斯科特在一起了
I know you're with Scott.
没错
I know.
但是你随时可以来找我
But you can come to me anytime.
你知道的 是吧
You know that, right?
我没事
I'm fine.
但是你说的没错
But you're right.
今晚真的很难熬
It's just been a really tough night.
我会再给他做一遍检查
I'm just gonna recheck his labs.
你已经戳了这家伙几回了
How many times did you stick this guy?
五次半了
Five...And a half.
他的静脉一直在移位 我的意思是
His vein keeps moving. I mean, it's --
就像是阻拦贾巴一样
it's literally like trying to stick Jabba the Hut.
也许再试两次你就能找到了
Maybe after two tries, you come find me next time.
尤其是经过这个晚上以后 保罗
Especially after the night you've had, Paul.
但愿他没有心脏病
Let's hope he doesn't have a heart attack, too.
先生您好
Hello, sir.
我是齐亚医生 让我看看我能为你做些什么
I'm Dr. Zia. Let's see if I can help you.
那些实习生不能做吗
Those kids don't know what they're doing.
呃 看来你的静脉对于他们来说是个挑战
Well, your veins do present a challenge.
向左边看并且屏住呼吸
Look over to the left and hold your breath, please.
你是那个割了包皮的人吗
Are you the doctor getting his huevos snipped?
我 我什么也没说 我发誓
I-I didn't say anything, I swear.
他没说 他只是一有人说蛋蛋就会脸红而已
He didn't. He blushes whenever anyone mentions balls.
永远别做绝育手术
Never get a vasectomy.
我就把包皮割了
I got snipped.
该死的医生说
Damn doctor said it would only hurt
它只会疼几天
for a couple of days.
大骗子
Liar!
感觉就像有人把喷灯放在我的丁丁上
Felt like somebody put a blowtorch on my man meat.
我几乎不能走路
I could barely walk.
一切再也回不到从前
And things were never the same again
那些羞羞的事情 你知道我的意思吧
in the bedroom, you know what I mean?
-许多情况都可能
-Ah. That could have been caused
导致这种结果  -不可能
by any number of conditions. -Nope.
以前我每早醒来都会搭帐篷
I used to wake up every morning with a flagpole,
直到我做了那个手术
until I got the big "V."
现在我一把一把的吃伟哥
Now I'm taking e.D. Pills by the truckload
但是收效甚微
just to get a little movement.
嗷
Ow!
对不起
Sorry.
在那边
Over here!
我们需要帮助 发生车祸了
We need some help! There was an accident!
需要救伤直升机 快把直升机停到这里来
He needs a medevac! Get the chopper here now!
放下来
Down. Yeah.
嘿 查理我们做到了
Hey, Charlie, we made it!
你将立即被送往医院
Okay? You're gonna be in the hospital in no time.
我们一会儿就会回去给你做检查
We'll come by and check on you.
谢谢你 医生
Thanks, doc.
现在你应该去看看那些骑警了
You...You should go for rangers, man.
他们有你这个救星真是太幸运了
They'd be lucky to have a guy like you.
好了 送他出去吧
All right, get him out of here.
我和他们谈了谈抓捕麦克的行动
I spoke to operations about Mike.
他们已经抓住了他 易如反掌
They already got him. He had it easy.
没错 毫无疑问
Yeah. No doubt.
去看看你的肩膀
-Hey, get that shoulder looked at.
也许需要动个手术 -好的
You might need surgery. -Sure.
你知道
You know...
查理是个白痴
Charlie can be an idiot.
我打赌他肯定不知道
I bet he's around gay guys all the time
他身边的人都是同性恋
and doesn't even know it.
但是他有件事情没错
He's right about one thing, though.
你是个孤胆英雄
You'd make one hell of a ranger.
很开心和你在一起工作 中尉
A pleasure serving with you, lieutenant.
亚历山大医生
Dr. Alexander.
这位是克莉丝汀
This is Christine. Hi.
她是那个病人 乔治的女朋友
She was John Doe's -- George's girlfriend.
他有双相情感障碍
He has bipolar disorder.
没错 我们就是因为这个分手的
Yeah, that's actually why we broke up.
他的病变得越来越棘手
Um...It just got really hard to deal with.
对不起 你说他有双相情感障碍
I'm sorry. You said bipolar.
克莉丝汀 他有在吃某种药吗
Christine, was he on any kind of medication?
没错 他在吃药 但是他讨厌副作用
Well, he was, but he hated the side effects of it.
这就是他来教堂的原因
So that's why he came to our church --
尝试某种消极治疗方法
to try a more holistic approach.
好的 你记得他吃的是哪种药吗
Okay, do you remember what kind it was?
是锂
It was... Lithium.
没错
Yeah.
什么时候开始停药的
When did he go off it?
也许 大概一个月以前
Maybe, like... A month ago.
我想我知道乔治得的是什么病了
I think I know what's going on with George.
我先走了
Um, excuse me.
现在马上去药房
Get the pharmacy. Now.
他癫痫发作了 一毫克苯妥英
He's having a seizure. A gram of dilantin, now.
他即将再次心动过速
He's going into v-tach again.
脉搏血压都在下降 吧急救包给我
Pulse ox is dropping. Hand me the ambu bag.
肯尼 注射25毫克丹曲林
Kenny, bolus 25 migs of dantrolene
开始给他精确注射
and start him on a versed drip.
挂一袋D5加上一半3安培的重碳酸盐
Hang a bag of d5 half with 3 amps bicarb.
他有双相情感障碍
He's bipolar.
他大约两周前停止服用锂
He stopped taking lithium abruptly two weeks ago,
一旦当你不能慢慢戒掉自己的
and when you don't slowly wean yourself
情绪稳定剂的时候 就会引起恶性综合征
off of mood stabilizers -- causes neuroleptic malignant syndrome.
做的不错
Nice catch.
责任不是全在我
It wasn't all me.
他的神游症和他的状态与此有关
So his fugue state was connected to his condition.
哈
Huh.
无论如何我觉得你需要一个神经科医生
I guess you did need a psychiatrist after all.
我错过了一些有趣的事儿 不是吗
I missed something juicy, didn't I?
克莉丝汀 听着 我知道你不相信
Christine, look, I know that you
任何医学治疗 但是
don't believe in medical treatment, but --
实际上 我相信
actually, I do believe in it.
实际上 我其实也相信
如果我有需要的话也会找医生
I go to doctors if I need them.
我只是想先试试祷告一下
I just prefer to try prayer first.
谢谢你救了乔治一命
Thanks for saving George.
兰德里 嘿 等一下
Landry, hey. Hold on a second.
对不起我刚刚叱责了你
I'm sorry for jumping on you earlier.
我那是无理取闹
It was uncalled-for.
你帮助救了乔治的命 而且
You helped save George, and...
没有你我不可能做得到
I couldn't have done it without you.
还有别的要说吗
Anything else?
听着 呃
Look, uh...
这个病例真的让我心烦意乱
This case really pushed my buttons.
在我15岁的时候 我爸得了重症的肺炎
When I was 15, my father contracted severe pneumonia.
他需要抗生素 到了最后还需要手术
He needed antibiotics and eventually surgery.
而且这病在当时很容易治疗
And it was very treatable.
可是他就是不肯
But he wouldn't do it.
他只想祷告
He just wanted to pray.
然后
And...
我妈妈也赞同
My mother agreed.
然后 我眼睁睁看着他死去
So...I watched him die.
我完全不知道这件事
I had no idea.
然后你就决定当医生是吗
And then you decided to be a doctor.
差不多吧
Something like that.
我真的 十分十分的抱歉
I am really, truly sorry
那么混蛋的对待你
for being such a bitch to you.
而我说的这些不能当做借口
And this isn't an excuse for my behavior.
这只是一个解释
It's just an explanation.
好吧 这解释十分合理
Well, it's a damn good one.
而且你早应该就告诉我
And you should've just told me that.
会对你有帮助的
It would have helped.
但是听着
But look...
我也很抱歉 关于这一切
I'm sorry, too -- about everything.
我不知道 我们以后会不会成为闺蜜
I don't know that -- that we'll ever be best friends,
但是 我愿意尝试至少跟你做工作上的小伙伴
but...I'd like to try to at least be work friends.
好的
Okay.
我倒可以接受
I can live with that.
嗯
Okay.
好吧
All right.
你好呀 帅哥 嗯
Hello, handsome. Mm.
训练怎么样呀
How was drill?
平平淡淡
Uneventful.
看见T.C.了没 我想和他谈谈
Have you seen t.C.? I want to talk to him
关于那个巡逻医护推荐的事
about that ranger recommendation.
噢 我以为你不想去竞争巡逻医护呢
Oh. I thought you were leaning on not going for ranger.
我原本是不想
I was.
但我现在觉得或许我需要他们
I just think I might need them
也许就和他们需要我一样
as much as they probably need me.
等下
Hold up.
噢 还平平淡淡呢 是吧
Oh! Uneventful, huh?
嗯
Mm-hmm.
嘿 快把每个细节都给我说的清清楚楚
Hey, I want to hear every detail,
跩逼中尉
lieutenant badass.
哇 好严重的伤呀
Whoa! That's nasty.
嗯 我打算让克里丝塔和保罗缝起来
Yeah, I figured I'd let Krista and Paul stitch it up,
让他们练习练习 怎样缝得整整齐齐的
get some practice in, nice and neat.
遵命 话说 保罗 他在哪呀
Yes. Speaking of, uh, where is he? Paul?
他在 很可能在生闷气呢吧
He's...Probably sulking.
他今天晚上可是被乔丹给虐惨了
He got spanked by Jordan tonight.
那才能让你们这群自以为什么都懂的家伙吸取教训
That's how you know-it-alls learn.
来吧 我们 呃 还有个事要做
Come on. There's, uh, something we have to do.
对啊
Yes!
噢 嘿 乔丹
Ooh. Hey, Jordan.
-最好快点了 -怎么了
-Better hurry up. -Why?
额 可能和蛋糕有关 只能说这么多啦
Huh, it might involve cake, is all I'm saying.
天哪你们 真不敢相信
You guys! I can't believe you...
足球
Soccer balls?
嗯 为托佛准备的
Yeah, they're for Topher.
纪念他的手术
Symbolic of his operation.
这样啊
Yum.
嘿 他要来了 要来了
Hey, he's coming, he's coming.
惊喜
Surprise! Surprise!
呜呼
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
噢 就像噩梦成真了似的
Oh! It's like a nightmare come true.
好吧 呃 谢谢呀
All right. Uh, thank you, I think.
啊 这些是按照原大小制作的 对不
Uh, those are actual size, right?
托佛 泌尿科在等着你
Topher, urology's ready for you.
好吧
All right.
你确定你要这么做吗 伙计
You sure you wanna do this, buddy?
嗯 对 我要 嗯
Yeah, yeah, I am. Yeah?
好吧
All right.
风萧萧兮易水寒
Dead man walking!
呵呵 很好笑
Right. That's funny.
对
Right.
挺 挺不错
That's...That's nice.
谢谢 所有人都在这里了
Thank you. Everybody's here...
完全没人管病人
And nobody's with the patients.
棒呆了
Fantastic.
回去工作去吧 各位
Back to work, everyone.
乔丹
Jordan.
我刚刚接到律师来电
I just got a call from legal.
他们让我告诉你急救员
They wanted me to tell you the paramedic
已经改了他的口供
has changed his story.
他说他不能保证
He says he can't swear
看到的那个是“请勿医治”手环
that it was a "Do not treat" Bracelet,
他说也有可能只是个运动手环
and it could have been a fuelband
或是其他类似的什么
or something like that.
他为什么要这样做
Why would he do that?
我倒是猜得出来
I could make a guess.
你感觉怎么样
How are you feeling?
实际上 还挺不错的
Actually, I'm fine.
那药还能让人领悟到点东西
It was enlightening.
的确
It can be.
你知道吗 我以前从未和别人说过这个 但是
You know, I never told anybody this, but...
我左眼有视力衰退的问题
I have some degenerative issues with my left eye.
你还真是知道怎么守好秘密啊
You do know how to keep a secret.
有多严重
How bad is it?
局部失明
Partial blindness,
现在因为模糊的视线而引起的
and now the headaches are getting worse
头疼越来越严重了
because of the blurred vision.
我一直在推迟矫正手术
I've been delaying corrective surgery.
为什么
Why?
害怕
Fear.
不过现在我觉得是时候解决它了
But now I think it's time I take care of it.
我准备离婚
I'm getting a divorce.
我和前妻协商好了 这样我就能见我的孩子们
I worked it out with my ex so I can see my kids.
这是新的篇章了
It's a new chapter.
我要从头开始
I'm starting over.
你这倒是很健康的心态
Well, that's a healthy attitude.
你有进步啦
You're making progress.
你介意一边吃早餐一边说吗
You care to talk about it over breakfast?
额
Um...
我
I'm...
我不是在泡你
I'm not asking you out.
就当做是对你不妥善标注药名的处罚吧
Consider it punishment for not labeling your meds properly.
好吧 那就走吧
All right. Let's do it.
#当那雾角响起#
♪When that foghorn blows♪
-#我便会回家#  -能听见你的声音真好
-♪I will be coming home♪  -it's so good to hear your voice.
我刚刚经历了有史以来最悲剧的一夜
I...I just had the worst night ever.
是这样的 有个家伙进来了 然后他
Yeah, well, this guy came in, and he was --
什么
what?
你什么意思 你想让我挂掉电话
What do you mean, you want me to hang up?
因为天上地下最好的男朋友
Because the world's best boyfriend's
就站在这
standing right over here.
#我无须再害怕 我#
♪Don't have to fear it, and I... ♪
你计划好了这一切 对不对
You planned this whole thing, didn't you?
嘿
Hi.
嗯 是呀
Yes, I did. Mmm.
#一如往日#
♪Just like way back in the days of old♪
嗯 我想死你了
Mmm. I missed you.
-生日快乐 宝贝  -谢啦
-Happy Birthday, baby. -Thank you.
-许个愿  -嗯
-Make a wish.  -Mmm.
#现在想停已经太迟#
♪And Its Too late to stop now♪
我就知道会有人记住我的生日的
I knew someone would remember my birth day.